

const faithMultiChoice = [
    
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "So then faith cometh by hearing, and hearing by the word of God.",
        options: ["Hebrews 11:1-3", "Habakkuk 2:4", "Ephesians 2:8-9", "Romans 10:17"],
        answer: "Romans 10:17",
        level: "easy"
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "Even so faith, if it hath not works, is dead, being alone.",
        options: ["James 1:3,6", "2 Timothy 2:13", "Hebrews 11:11", "James 2:17"],
        answer: "James 2:17",
        level: "easy"
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "For we walk by faith, not by sight.",
        options: ["Hebrews 11:1-3", "John 20:29", "1 John 5:4", "2 Corinthians 5:7"],
        answer: "2 Corinthians 5:7",
        level: "easy"
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "Jesus said unto him, 'If thou canst believe, all things are possible to him that believeth.'",
        options: ["James 2:17", "Matthew 21:22", "Mark 9:23", "Matthew 17:20-21"],
        answer: "Mark 9:23",
        level: "intermediate"
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "Behold, his soul which is lifted up is not upright in him: but the just shall live by his faith.",
        options: ["Ephesians 2:8-9", "Habakkuk 2:4", "Hebrews 11:6", "Hebrews 11:1-3"],
        answer: "Habakkuk 2:4",
        level: "intermediate"
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "If we believe not, yet he abideth faithful: he cannot deny himself.",
        options: ["2 Timothy 2:13", "Hebrews 11:11", "Jude 1:21", "James 1:3,6"],
        answer: "2 Timothy 2:13",
        level: "intermediate"
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "For whatsoever is born of God overcometh the world: and this is the victory that overcometh the world, even our faith.",
        options: ["John 20:29", "1 John 5:4", "John 3:16", "Hebrews 11:1-3"],
        answer: "1 John 5:4",
        level: "intermediate"
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "And all things, whatsoever ye shall ask in prayer, believing, ye shall receive.",
        options: ["Ephesians 2:8-9", "Matthew 21:22", "Matthew 17:20-21", "James 2:17"],
        answer: "Matthew 21:22",
        level: "intermediate"
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "For by grace are ye saved through faith, and that not of yourselves. It is the gift of God - not of works, lest any man should boast.",
        options: ["Ephesians 2:8-9", "Hebrews 11:6", "Hebrews 11:1-3", "Malachi 3:1"],
        answer: "Ephesians 2:8-9",
        level: "difficult"
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "Knowing this, that the trying of your faith works patience...But let him ask in faith, nothing wavering. For he that wavers is like a wave of the sea driven with the wind and tossed.",
        options: ["Hebrews 11:11", "Romans 10:17", "James 1:3,6", "1 Kings 20:3"],
        answer: "James 1:3,6",
        level: "difficult"
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        question: "Now faith is the substance of things hoped for, the evidence of things not seen. For by it the elders obtained a good report. Through faith we understand that the worlds were framed by the word of God, so that things which are seen were not made of things which do appear.",
        options: ["Revelation 2:12", "1 John 5:4", "Hebrews 11:1-3", "John 20:29"],
        answer: "Hebrews 11:1-3",
        level: "difficult"
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        question: "And Jesus said unto them, Because of your unbelief: for verily I say unto you, If ye have faith as a grain of mustard seed, ye shall say unto this mountain, Remove hence to yonder place; and it shall remove; and nothing shall be impossible unto you. Howbeit this kind goeth not out but by prayer and fasting.",
        options: ["Mark 9:23", "Matthew 17:20-21", "James 2:17", "Ephesians 2:8-9"],
        answer: "Matthew 17:20-21",
        level: "difficult"
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        question: "But without faith it is impossible to please him: for he that cometh to God must believe that he is, and that he is a rewarder of them that diligently seek him.",
        options: ["Hebrews 11:6", "Hebrews 11:1-3", "Habakkuk 2:4", "Ephesians 2:8-9"],
        answer: "Hebrews 11:6",
        level: "intermediate"
    },
    {
        id: 14,
        question: "Through faith also Sara herself received strength to conceive seed, and was delivered of a child when she was past age, because she judged him faithful who had promised.",
        options: ["2 Timothy 2:13", "Romans 10:17", "James 1:3,6", "Hebrews 11:11"],
        answer: "Hebrews 11:11",
        level: "difficult"
    },
    {
        id: 15,
        question: "Jesus saith unto Him, 'Thomas, because thou hast seen me, thou hast believed: Blessed are they taht have not seen, and yet have believed.",
        options: ["1 John 5:4", "Genesis 2:3", "John 20:29", "Romans 8:31"],
        answer: "John 20:29",
        level: "difficult"
    },
    {
        id: 16,
        question: "Even so faith, if it has not works, is dead, being alone.",
        options: ["Ephesians 2:8-9", "James 2:17", "Mark 9:23", "Matthew 21:22"],
        answer: "Ephesians 2:8-9",
        level: "intermediate"
    }
]

export default faithMultiChoice;